Definitely, I mean, life didn't know it
was so real, you know, as as a kid, you
know,
want to be in NFL, want, you know, play,
get drafted, you know, just just
get that phone call,
see my name called, you know, just
meant so much to me and my family.
You played for a couple schools. How do
you think that helped prepare you for
what you're going to see in the NFL?
Uh I think actually a lot, you know,
just um being in different locker rooms,
you know, from from guys from, you know,
uh Texas to to California to
Mississippi. So, I think first like the
whole team bonding thing, you know, uh
will be easy. And then secondly, I mean,
just like getting to know different uh
defenses and and play books as well from
Old Miss to Oregon and Tulane. I think
just learning, you know, um
a lot of variety uh was uh helpful as
well.
We'll go next to Sam McDowell. Sam?
Hey, what's up, Maddie? It It seems like
you moved around the field a little bit,
especially in the secondary. I'm just
wondering if you could share where you
feel most comfortable and and just the
process of of trying to get comfortable
in multiple spots.
Yeah, to me, I mean, you know, corner's
fine, star's fine, free's fine, you
know, um I don't have a I don't have
like a one spot, you know, I'm I'm good
at. Um like I'm comfortable at uh all
all five, honestly.
And we just talked to the scouts here
for the Chiefs who talked about your
special teams. What kind of pride do you
take in in playing in those phases?
Yeah, a lot. I mean, throughout my
career, you know, um
I've had coaches, you know, who value
that like defense offense as well. So,
you know, if it's gunner, if it's hold
up, you know, if it's
uh KR, you know, I I I take pride in it
a lot.
We'll go next to Matt Derrick. Matt?
Hey, Jayden. Congratulations.
Thank you. What was your draft
experience like? Uh you know, what was
your What were you doing out there? You
you just celebrate or celebrating with
your friends and family?
Uh yes, I was. So, um I had a little
party um
by the beach called uh the Brix and uh
my family and uh friends came out uh
show love and support.
You And you mentioned the you know,
playing the star and the Chiefs scouts
mentioned that, you know, the nickel is
especially where they they view you.
What is it you like about the nickel?
What What makes you feel feel like that
that's a a good position for you?
Um I think just the ability, you know,
to to cover and the ability just to
read and react, you know, on certain
plays, you know, if it's a pass or run
play. And I feel like, you know, that
spot, you know, just allows you to play
freely, you know,
and fast.
We'll go to Jessie Newell next. Jessie?
Hey, Jayden. I just wondered how much
familiarity you had with the Chiefs
coming to this whole process and um you
know, if you were expecting this sort of
call from them today.
Right. I mean, cuz Andy, you know, is is
from the Kansas City. He's a big fan. Uh
he loves them. I mean, he told me like
me number of times how
he wanted me to you know, to play for
his uh childhood team, you know. And um
I think me and Coach Spagnola and the
whole uh DB core kind of zoomed for like
a hour or whatnot. So, I met with um met
with Coach Spagnola, the DB coach as
well. Also the special teams coach and
then a few um
uh
other guys as well.
We'll go to Matt Foster next. Matt?
Hey, Jayden. Welcome to uh Kansas City.
Um I I told you. How do you feel like
having played in both the SEC and Big 10
against some of the best competition
that college football has to offer has
prepared you to make this jump to the
NFL?
Um well, I think I I I engaged me
started pretty early cuz I'm from
Florida.
Um so, I see a lot of the five-star guys
and big name guys at a young age. So, um
I think when I got to college, you know,
I wasn't like surprised about seeing,
you know, guys who were supposed to be,
you know, first-round grades or like
guys, you know, bigger name but um you
know, obviously, you know, seeing
Ja'Marr Chase or, you know, Jedis, you
know, definitely make me like, "Oh,
wow." And then after you see them, you
know, you'll lock back in, you know. Um
but no, I think playing in those
conferences definitely
helped me out um a lot.
It looks like that is all the questions
that we have for you. Congratulations.
Welcome to Kansas City. Go enjoy.
We'll do it. Yes, ma'am. Talk to you
soon. Okay.